<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Mike&#39;s Health Log</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/dad/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mike&#39;s Health Log</description>
    <image>
      <title>Mike&#39;s Health Log</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/dad/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dad/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.140.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:56:52 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/dad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Saturday Dec 21, 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/007-saturday-dec-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:56:52 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/007-saturday-dec-21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I got back to the hospital around 7am to relieve Katelyn and bring her breakfast. Dad slept through the night, but spent much of Saturday napping and watching football. He&amp;rsquo;s got a sense of humor still, even if it takes him longer to grasp what was said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We expected to hear from case management/social work on Friday, but they didn&amp;rsquo;t come around until today. He&amp;rsquo;s got options around skilled nursing facilities, so we&amp;rsquo;ll need to make a decision very soon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday Dec 20, 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/006-friday-dec-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:47:51 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/006-friday-dec-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The night before was a long night. I didn&amp;rsquo;t sleep much, and the chair in the room wasn&amp;rsquo;t the most comfortable, but it certainly could have been far worse. Dad slept a lot of the night, but woke up a number of times when staff had to do things like take vitals or give him a breathing treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outpouring of support from mom&amp;rsquo;s church family and friends was nearly overwhelming. The meals, well wishes, kind words, and friendly faces really has been a blessing through all this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thursday Dec 19, 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/005-thursday-dec-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:42:14 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/005-thursday-dec-19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;They extubated dad on Thursday, and things started moving what felt quickly. His fever was down and he was more or less off sedation fully at this point. He was still weak, and it was even more difficult to understand him, but that can be attributed to a myraid of factors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Around 9 in the evening, they moved dad from ICU to &amp;ldquo;tele&amp;rdquo;, which is a step down unit from ICU. Because he was covid positive on intake, he was put into an isolation room. The good news here is that visitors can be there 24 hours a day. Given that mom had been at the hospital nearly all day every day since, and Emily and Caleb were feeling sick, I stayed with dad this first night out of ICU.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wednesday Dec 18, 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/004-wednesday-dec-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:35:42 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/004-wednesday-dec-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The ICU doctors stopped his sedation on Wednesday and performed another breathing test. His infection and sepsis were not really getting better, but also it wasn&amp;rsquo;t any worse than the previous days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The breathing test went well, and the doctors were considering extubating him. He spent most of the day weak, in and out of sleep, but that could have been residual effects of the sedation meds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday Dec 17, 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/003-tuesday-dec-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:28:53 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/003-tuesday-dec-17/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not much change on Tuesday, either. The doctors in ICU were optimistic about getting him off the vent on Tuesday or Wednesday, but his sepsis and infection were holding steady.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monday Dec 16, 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/002-monday-dec-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:07:56 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/002-monday-dec-16/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Monday, we found out his diagnosis included sepsis in addition to the covid and pneumonia. Beyond that, there was no real developments on Monday. We did spend most of the day in and out of ICU with him, but he was sedated, so I&amp;rsquo;m not sure he even really knew we were there.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunday Dec 15, 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/001-sunday-dec-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:07:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dad/posts/001-sunday-dec-15/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dad went into cardiac arrest in the middle of the night. Caleb was, thankfully, around to start aid, and he worked with the paramedics to provide CPR and get dad into an ambulance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was taken to Baptist Hospital, and admitted to the ER, then eventually ICU, and put on a ventilator. Diagnosis at the time was Covid and pneumonia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Katelyn and I packed up the truck and the dogs, and we drove 11 and a half hours, arriving in Beaumont in the early hours of Monday morning. ICU visiting hours at Baptist are 9 to 9, though, so we didn&amp;rsquo;t get to see dad until Monday.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
